{ "backgroundcolor":"#000000",
 "height":33,
 "layers":[
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJztmkEOgyAQRdl5IG\/fpT2NO49gmpTUEMAZpJnP8Bdv1Zo8eFM0jXsIYSfEOYcSuv3cNoB+2836tXvYss+9G1n4tcwkWn\/Sd27uZoj9\/SE9Oxag\/gtRI+lf+s4G0v46A0RPS3+09ukMWHuM5qXpvwKv5\/3F2mMUr9hxZf8pvXL90++wv18vSf90Btjfj5fk\/Gd\/v17sP7dXqX9tBtjfjxf7z+3F\/nN7sf\/cXtLnP\/b36fX0+X8FWEPklWDtg+6Vdhy9\/8cn\/s6QziZUr1L\/Wnv29+PF\/nN7sf\/cXtL7P\/v79GrtfwTM\/um7bdY+6F7X\/rV3wHKfXWeA6LDuHqm1l5wB8V5AdCDMQO7Ml\/7\/S56B0v\/OM3ed9d55YIT+peta1vuP+Wn1k+wN+\/fZo957bbVXrU4o\/tr1WfsQHE6HGj45",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":33,
         "name":"back",
         "opacity":0.5,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":128,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJztmkEOgzAMBHPrg\/h9j7yoT6hyiGRFxI4dAhvYkfbWwpKxaFRIiZDn83Pm7d3k+faLzqmRO2hr4F3DyDqf7eiOfpFeiP6Z8+ZGcvR5+n9ealreS+4md\/gwrhR3ln9094WdCcfjH9F9gb18tGZAQv\/joPfy+N8S\/vWggd4rO+3d+9G\/H\/Remv+U6H8U9F7Sv3UPoH8\/6L3ofy7ovWr\/2gzQvx\/0XvQ\/F\/Re9D8X9F70Pxf0Xtb+LyX6HwG9V3T\/v11Ts4tvFRRQe9UeV\/dPfLT812j\/\/9L\/utD\/u6H\/d9P7+689\/6f\/dZH+o+9\/IPmv329DAbWX5l\/OgPX+H+MLCpp76x4gZ2BjXEGYAct9zz6QiQXFv9XziLvX7glZwX+LyPWOfv\/Mfj3Qv82II+9xPMebQbQTSn+LVXqS6\/kDSRmk0g==",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":33,
         "name":"front",
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":128,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#5555ff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"mods",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":709,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel",
                     "front":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":208
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":710,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":711,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":256,
                 "x":688,
                 "y":216
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":712,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel",
                     "front":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":48
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":713,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":256,
                 "x":80,
                 "y":40
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":714,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":735,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":952,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":759,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":760,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":761,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":772,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":672,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":40,
                 "id":773,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedscrappanel",
                     "colorVariant":"6"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "colorVariant":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":16,
                 "x":656,
                 "y":160
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":774,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":648,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":775,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "colorVariant":"7",
                     "front":"ledgebrick"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "colorVariant":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":32,
                 "x":648,
                 "y":152
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":779,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":784,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":64,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":786,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":368,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":40,
                 "id":787,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedscrappanel",
                     "colorVariant":"6"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "colorVariant":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":16,
                 "x":352,
                 "y":160
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":788,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "colorVariant":"7",
                     "front":"ledgebrick"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "colorVariant":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":32,
                 "x":344,
                 "y":152
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":789,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":344,
                 "y":56
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"objects",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":5900,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":782,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":640,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":5900,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":790,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":336,
                 "y":200
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ffff00",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"wiring - lights & guns",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"monsters & npcs",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#00ffff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"wiring - locked door",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"outside the map",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"anchors etc",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":244,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":752,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":816,
                 "y":256
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":244,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":753,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":208,
                 "y":16
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":245,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":756,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":245,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":757,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":640,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":245,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":770,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":168
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":245,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":794,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":944,
                 "y":168
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"items",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }],
 "nextobjectid":795,
 "orientation":"orthogonal",
 "renderorder":"right-down",
 "tiledversion":"1.0.2",
 "tileheight":8,
 "tilesets":[
        {
         "firstgid":1,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/materials.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":196,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/supports.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":232,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/miscellaneous.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":254,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/liquids.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":282,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/ancient.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":444,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/apex.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":815,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/avian.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":1120,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/floran.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":1315,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/generic.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3241,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/glitch.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3467,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/human.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3751,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/hylotl.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3983,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/novakid.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4046,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/breakable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4354,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/decorative.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5773,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/door.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5901,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/farmable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5976,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/furniture.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6322,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/light.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6764,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/railpoint.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6769,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/teleporter.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6809,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/trap.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7013,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/wire.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7231,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/container.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7513,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/teleporter.json"
        }],
 "tilewidth":8,
 "type":"map",
 "version":1,
 "width":128
}